The pursuers might have someone who knows magic.
They can sense us remotely.
My lord,
the barking is getting closer.
Half an incense stick of time at most.
Baiyun Temple is twenty miles east of the city.
There might be a way to break the pact there.
You must take the official road to get there.
The pursuers will definitely set an ambush.
And it's unknown whether the people in the temple are friends or foes.
I...
I remember my father mentioning it.
Daoist Lu of Baiyun Temple
is Uncle Shen's sworn brother.
He is trustworthy.
We can't take the official road.
Half a mile downstream along the riverbank,
I remember there is a reed marsh.
We can hide there until dawn.
Then we'll take the mountain path to Baiyun Temple.
You and Miss Gu are connected by the mark.
If she loses control,
you will be affected too.
You must stay awake.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Baiyun Temple is currently
our only clue.
If Uncle Lu is really a piece you left behind,
please protect us.
The smoke condenses and doesn't dissipate.
It contains special medicinal powder.
It's the purifying incense commonly used by Daoists.
This talisman is indeed
an authentic product of Baiyun Temple.
I...
I just seemed to hear
a voice in my head saying...
Tell Shen Mo,
The ledger is under the founder's statue.
The copper coin is in his arms.
Are you Young Master Shen Mo?
Uncle Lu asked me to wait here.
Come in quickly.
The pursuers are almost here.
My lord,
beware of a trap.
Thank you, young Daoist.
We'll come in right away.
Stay close to me.
Act according to the situation.
Registrar Shen,
I've been waiting for a long time.
Lord Qin predicted you would come here.
Qin Muzhi's subordinate.
Your disguise skills are too poor.
Young Daoist,
pretending must be hard on you.
Go!
Mo'er!
Run!
It's a trap.
They captured all the disciples in the temple
and forced me to lure you out.
Daoist Lu,
don't forget your disciples.
Qin Muzhi colluded with the Third Prince
to seize what brother Shen Qingshan left behind,
the account book and the copper coin.
The book holds evidence of them funding evil arrays
and trading officials' lives.
The copper coin is one of three tokens.
Combined, they reveal Tianji Pavilion's location.
Mo'er,
you must not let them succeed.
Uncle Lu,
you talk too much.
Shen Mo,
hand over your two blood chalcedonies.
Tell us what you found in Gu Wenyuan's secret room,
and we will leave Lu Mingyuan a whole corpse.
Otherwise,
the 12 Daoists in the temple,
including this child,
will die before you one by one.
You laid an ambush here,
fearing I'd meet Daoist Lu
and get clues.
So,
the account book and copper coin
haven't been found by you, right?
Did you know
the mother contract on Miss Gu
might be connected
to one of you?
Qin Muzhi masters soul control.
Haven't you death soldiers
been planted with child contracts?
If Miss Gu triggers the mother contract now,
all of you
might suffer a backlash.
You protect Miss Gu and Xiaocui.
Rush to the main hall's left corridor.
There is a side door.
I'll save Uncle Lu.
My lord.
Go!
Go to the secret passage behind the main hall.
I'll hold them off.
Uncle Lu!
Brother Qingshan gave me a second life.
Today, I shall repay him.
Mo'er,
remember.
When three coins unite,
the map to Tianji Pavilion will appear.
Behind Qin Muzhi is the Imperial Astronomy Bureau.
Go!
Mo'er,
when you grow up, be like your father.
Be an upright
and discerning official.
Brother Lu,
if anything happens to me,
I entrust Mo'er to you.
Why say that, Brother Qingshan?
We are brothers,
sharing life and death together.
Brother Qingshan,
I am coming to find you.
Shen Mo,
you can't escape.
Lord Qin has cast an inescapable net.
Imperial Clan Court.
Tianji Pavilion.
Uncle Lu said three coins unite,
the map appears.
My lord,
the mark is burning.
We can't leave through the exit.
This secret passage
should have other branches.
Let's go look over there.